[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Huh.
Toby, what's going on?
So the sun slapped you in the face?
Why didn't you call the Sheriff?
Well, call him again.
It's 6:00 AM.
They should be in a U-Haul halfway out of Lawndale
and not slapping you in the face.
That's assault. 10-year-olds are just
as dangerous as 20-year-olds.
You know that.
Hey, I've got to go.
I'll call you later.
[HUMPH]
[GIGGLING]
[KISS]
[MOAN]
[DRILL]
[UGH] Just give me a moment.
[SIGH] There is never a dull moment.
Hm.
I wasn't expecting you up so early.
It's 4 o'clock.
Half the day's behind us.
You know who you look like?
You look just like your father.
You have the same nose
Huh.
Fortunately, that's all I inherited.
What do you mean?
He was never a provider, never really supported us.
He just kind of left us to fend for ourselves.
No milk money, no babysitting money, no gas money.
He just hit the road after 10 years.
You never even saw his feet hit the ground.
Well, your feet are mounted in cement.
Ariel is too fortunate to have you as an Uncle Richard.
Sure.
You know, I heard he ended some clown at Circus Circus
when my mother sought payback for his philandering
disposition.
She got a girlfriend because he had so many.
She got a boyfriend because he had so many girlfriends.
He saw them going into this room,
and he just transformed into quite a fellow.
He pummeled the poor douche with a lead pipe
and sent him into a coma for six months.
He evaded the cops in a Bronco.
Actually, I think it was a Corvette.
It should have been a Bronco.
He never harmed my mother like most jealous men would have.
That's the last I heard of him.
I wish I had known him.
You know, I found a picture of him
with my mom and another woman.
He cheated with her too.
She came to my mother's funeral, and cousin Ellen
used to call her Aunt Yolanda.
My mother would roll over in her grave if she saw me now.
If she saw you now, she'd be proud of you.
Because of my rolling estate, my Bowflex bod, or my trophy
girlfriend?
Shower?
Mm.
I like my space.
[GIGGLING]
All right.
Whew.
[WATER RUNNING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(OFFSCREEN) Dammit.
(YELLING) Shit!
[BANG]
(OFFSCREEN) What's up?
Bumped my knee.
(OFFSCREEN) Be careful out there.
Remember how you told me you despise CDs?
Yeah.
It's weak interest, and short term,
and it's not a sufficient investment.
What would be sufficient?
Where would you invest your money?
Freshen up.
Don't forget your glasses on your way out.
You know, you said ask if I needed help.
Well, your help is needed.
Richard!
So that's it, huh?
That's our link?
Staring at my Nordic tattoo while your pelvis
smacks against my ass?
You forgot to thank the Academy.
You know, if you have issues, I've got short term loans.
You can pay back, no interest.
You're an asshole.
[BANG]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Another fit of rage?
You know my feelings about that.
Money's frivolous.
Those were your words.
You know, maybe we shouldn't date.
Ruby?
Oh, no.
[GRUNT]
Don't forget the bags in the trunk.
I can't wait to take a shower.
Long night.
Do you notice that mess on the garage floor?
No.
Devin, check it out.
It's eggshells.
Probably that kid from across the street.
Let's go inside.
Oh, shit.
[DOOR SQUEAKING]
Oh, I'm glad Grandma's fine.
[INAUDIBLE]?
Not much.
Smoking is prohibited.
At Bennigan's the cops tasered some World War II geezer
for puffing on a Colombian.
Gosh.
Where's you boyfriend?
Devin, what's the problem?
The bag got stuck.
Where do you want them, Mrs. Warren?
Not there.
Upstairs.
Oh, it's OK, Devin.
Just put it in the closet.
Richard!
Did you ask him?
Not yet, but I will.
Oh, are you guys hungry?
No.
We are.
Ariel.
A little.
[UGH] Go make him something.
I'm going upstairs to change.
[KNOCKING]
Richard?
Richard.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[KNOCKING]
Richard.
[GRUNT]
I was sleeping.
Do you mind?
You're home early.
I know.
I'm tired.
This is shameful.
I'm sorry.
I was expecting you tomorrow.
TSA let you on board with that?
Ariel just gave it back.
[SIGH] How was your trip?
Exhausting.
What time are Jahira and Fernando coming?
Oh, 30 minutes.
30 minutes?
Uh-huh.
You're home early.
[GRUNT] I caught an earlier flight.
Don't you check your voicemail?
Ariel and Devin downstairs?
Mm-hm.
When are they leaving?
I don't know.
30 minutes?
Did you have to hang your things here?
They reek of garlic.
You want to bathe in it?
I'm going to go to the study.
Oh, Ariel has something to ask you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[DISHES RATTLING]
Hey!
You look fit.
Bowflex has been kind.
I was going to come up there, but you came down here.
Wow.
No, Devin.
No, not that one.
The other one.
No, the other one.
When are you leaving?
Just give it to me.
After this.
Where?
Lake Elsinore.
Yo, Doug, you see that order?
Keep in that order.
Excuse us a second.
[PHONE NOTIFICATION]
Go to the car.
Sir.
OK, I have a favor.
I was wondering.
Mm.
You can't stand.
You really want money?
You can't stand on your feet?
What's a student to do?
Work for me.
Only a celery stick is in my fridge, and a dollar in my bank
account.
Why are you going to Lake Elsinore?
Is that paying for it?
Yeah, paying he is, but LAUSD displaced him.
[SIGH] How much?
$500.
I'll hit you back.
I can't keep bailing you out.
I need this break.
I've given you thousands of dollars of breaks.
Please.
[UGH] OK, you're right.
What are you doing?
No money, no trip.
You're right.
I need to start learning to cut back.
So me and Devin will just stay here and watch TV.
Here.
Thank you.
Put $1,500 in your account for Monday.
Will that hold you?
Yes.
How's school?
Awesome.
I took your advice.
I changed my major to business.
America is capital, like you said.
Right.
[SIGH] You better get moving.
Traffic is going to be fast and busy.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Yes.
[INAUDIBLE]
Yay.
[SIGH] See you around.
[SIGH]
[CAR ENGINE STARTING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
Can I help you, Officer?
Is that a yacht?
It's a boat.
Is there something I can do for you?
Are you Mr. Warren?
Yeah.
Is there a problem?
Yeah, well, my unit pursued a degenerate this morning.
And she nabbed that car right outside your driveway.
And we received a tip that she is sequestered somewhere
in this neighborhood.
Have you heard anything?
This is a recent photograph of the suspect.
Do you recognize her?
Wow.
What is big glasses?
Yeah, she resembles Ugly Betty.
But you know, those glasses are where that resemblance ends.
Her antics resemble La Femme Nikita.
She's treacherous, she's a complete [? goon, ?]
and she's a sociopath.
She leaves wallets, slits throats,
and smiles just break in a new butterfly knife.
Now, if you don't mind, I'd like to search your home.
You're not a captive, are you?
No.
She has not been tickling my throat
with her butterfly knife.
Besides, don't you need a search warrant?
Not with your permission.
Is there a problem, mister?
Maybe because we received word that we will barricade
this neighborhood if anything suspicious or anyone acts
suspicious.
You know what?
I-
Listen, I know it's an inconvenience,
but sorry for the trouble.
It may be a false alarm, but it's a pain in the ass.
But your safety is my concern.
Yet my C.O. insists.
She may already have fled the area,
and one can't be too sure.
I just want to be sure we could check off your property,
and make sure she's not camouflaged in the walk-in
somewhere.
Yes?
Sure.
Are you expecting any guests?
Just my housekeepers.
When are they due?
10, 15 minutes.
Why, Officer Murphy?
Just be a moment.
Listen, the potato head across the street
always makes bogus phone calls, sends
illustrious cops on wild goose chases.
[LAUGHS] Well, thankfully, illustrious doesn't include me.
Can I go upstairs?
Can I tag along?
It's your house.
Tell me, mister, how much is this place worth?
That's a reason?
$10 to $12 million.
AKA, just mind my business.
Got it, Mr.
[HAIRDRYER]
Is someone taking a shower?
That's my better half.
May I?
Sure.
[HAIRDRYER]
[KNOCKING]
I'm sorry.
I'm basically intercepting a call.
OK.
Um.
Is everything fine?
Everything is fine.
I'm just concerned for your safety.
Mm-hm.
One other thing, do you recognize this person?
No.
But if I see her, you'll be the first to know.
Officer, I think that's a whole house.
(PHONE) You have a new text message.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
I have to take this call.
[CLICK]
Sorry about that.
Where were we?
I said, I think that's the whole house.
I really don't think so.
It smells.
Why do you think my wife was in there?
I can take it if you can.
Officer, my time.
Is there a problem, Mr.?
I'll be quick.
Then I'll be out of your hair.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You wear glasses?
It's my wife's.
What are you doing?
I'm almost done.
Officer, whoever you're looking for isn't here,
so let's just call it a day.
OK?
Ma'am.
Richard, next time, make sure your house
guest remembers her glasses.
[SLAM]
Well, I guess the perpetrator isn't here.
Well, maybe she's at another house.
Maybe.
But you know what I find funny, Mr., and find very surprising?
Your wife's reaction.
[LAUGHS] It's PMS.
You know what?
I confronted my ex-wife about the same similar situation,
and she had said that the suit had magically
appeared in my closet.
She said it was magic.
You two must have apprenticed with the same magician.
OK, good day, Mr. Warren.
(ANNOUNCER ON TV) This is field reporter Terry
Handelman coming to you live from Carson, California.
I'm standing in front of this residence
where a large crowd has chained themselves to a fence,
while the L.A. County Sheriffs post in front of the house.
This is in response to an initial conflict beginning
early this morning when the residents assaulted
this man after refusing to vacate the property.
First, can you tell us your name, sir?
(MAN ON TV) Sure Toby Mitchell.
(ANNOUNCER ON TV) Mr. Mitchell.
(MAN ON TV) Please, call me Toby.
(ANNOUNCER ON TV) OK, Toby.
[GASP]
Shut up.
It's not what you think.
Is that the woman in that picture?
Yes.
She knocked on the door and asked for help.
[INAUDIBLE],, she was totally beaten dead.
And nearsighted?
You.
You had to bring one of them here?
So you kill her?
No, no, no.
I did not kill anyone.
So I can ask them to go.
Oh, my god.
She's only been dead for a few minutes.
I can take her to the hospital.
They'll believe it was an accident.
No one has to go to jail.
You won't have to go to jail?
Listen, cover for me.
OK?
Please.
I need you.
(ANNOUNCER ON TV) There are millions
of people who are victims of mortgage fraud.
(MAN ON TV) Victims?
Now they're the victims?
I'm the one who got sucker punched by a fifth grader,
in the balls, too.
Can I see that on TV?
Where are the cops?
They should have been here.
Fernando, Jahira.
Buenos dias, senor.
Good morning.
Ready to work?
Yes.
We'll be in and out really quick.
Listen, I've got something for you.
Today, you get the day off.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] We so need the day off.
My sister is about to have my sobrino.
We could use the day off.
Would we be paid?
Hm.
No, not if you don't stay.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
How long is this going to take?
10, 15 minutes.
Do you need us to hurry?
Mm.
No.
No hurry.
Can we discuss my salary?
Salary?
Now?
Yes, sir.
[SIGH] Just give me a few minutes.
Whew.
Hey!
Hey.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, senor.
Conversation seems interesting.
Si.
[SIGH]
Well, senora and I were just talking
about how you can't wait for sobrina to have babies.
Yeah.
Hm.
Really?
While vacuuming?
Fine, you caught me.
I didn't say anything.
I was just here, listening to her.
But then, you know, I told her that I really have to finish.
Oh.
Are you finished now?
[? Yeah. ?]
Go clean the other rooms.
Yeah.
[INAUDIBLE]
[SIGH]
I thought you were getting rid of them.
Ex that.
I hope you didn't say anything.
I don't want to ruin your life, but I'm leaving.
Just give me your cell phone.
What are you doing?
Give it back.
Listen, a cop's outside.
None of us can leave right now.
I can't let you leave.
Look, if I send them home now, or if one of us splits,
this guy's going to get suspicious.
So please.
You have 15 minutes.
You're a jerk.
Mr. Warren, can I speak with you, please?
I'd like to renegotiate our rate.
Renegotiate now?
Until we do, I won't return.
In case you haven't been scoping the news,
the unemployment office has a line around the block.
So I hope this wasn't a threat.
I'm not threatening you, sir.
We're just dissatisfied with the arrangements.
Dissatisfied with a stud like you?
Your wife should be satisfied.
Not cool.
Listen, right now is not the time, Fernando.
Then we leave.
Jahira!
[SIGH] How much?
$250 per month.
That sounds steep.
So were those stairs I just vacuumed.
I break my back for you, sir.
So does my wife.
We even came despite our sister's pregnancy.
This isn't unreasonable.
You work hard for me.
I appreciate it.
Unfortunately, the economy has weathered us all, so no raises.
Sorry.
[VACUUM]
Excuse me.
Jahira!
[VACUUM]
[GRUNT] Where's Mrs. Warren?
Senor, [INAUDIBLE]?
She's in the bed, senor.
Listen, don't clean this room.
OK?
Why, Sir?
I'm almost done.
Well, the lights are broken, so I don't
want you to get electrocuted.
Oh, come on, senor.
I wanted the day off to go see my sister have my nephew,
and you wouldn't give me the day off unless I worked,
because if not, you wouldn't pay me.
Come on.
At least let me finish.
If you don't stop, you're finished.
Wait, don't do that.
Don't do that.
This is what has you all stressed out, senor?
[LAUGHS] [CLEARS THROAT]
Everything all right?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Everything's fine, big guy.
You got me.
Mrs. Is really jealous, so I just didn't want her to know.
Look, I have two brothers, two sons, and a husband.
Trust me.
I understand.
[INAUDIBLE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(WHISPERING) In the closet.
Everything fine, Mr. Warren?
Sure.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
Yeah.
I'll be right up.
Jahira.
Hey, honey.
You can put it right there.
OK.
Gracias, amor.
[SIGH]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[VACUUM]
[GRUNT]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Excuse me.
Hey.
Oh.
[HEAVY BREATHING] Aye, senor, you scared me at the same time.
I'm [? kidding. ?]
Sorry.
Listen, your husband's waiting for you downstairs.
Wait, look!
Look, look.
I just a picture.
Hey.
Show me on the way down.
My nephew!
Look!
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Is that her first?
No.
No, it's her third.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Is she excited?
Oh, my god.
You're excited when you have your first one.
Man, when you had your first baby,
it's like your first day in kindergarten.
Can you just imagine that, how exciting that is?
Then you have your second one.
Oh, bye, senora.
Bye.
Hm.
Mm.
She's not talking a lot lately, huh?
I don't know.
Is she OK?
Yeah.
Are you guys going on vacation or something?
Got her down here.
But yeah, when you have your third kid,
oh, you know exactly what to do, how
to take care of your amigo or your amiga,
because you have it down by then.
Excellent.
So what bothered you in the closet?
Oh, you know, I thought I saw some eyes.
Eyes?
Yeah, in the closet.
I thought I saw some eyes looking at me.
You must be tired.
Yeah, well, I was in the hospital
until 3:00 in the morning.
Can you imagine?
Yeah.
Si,
OK.
So, senor, how is Ariel these days?
Oh, she's good.
Yeah.
Is she still with that boyfriend of hers?
Yeah, he makes her happy.
The teacher?
Yeah.
He's an idiot, but he's just her type.
Well, I hope things get better for her.
Yeah.
Fernando, you do such awesome work.
Thank you.
My hands are dirty.
[LAUGHS] Well, thank you, senor.
Oh, and can you please tell the Mrs. That it's a boy?
I'll tell her.
Please.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Jahira, [INAUDIBLE] waiting for us.
OK, let's go.
Bye, senor!
Bye.
[SIGH]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
What are you doing?
Deciding what I need.
Listen, you need to stay.
Mm-mm.
You know, thanks for the move.
Jahira was taking clues.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
Write me a check.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Write me a check.
You know, we both know you'll be back.
Get rid of her.
[CAR DOOR DINGING]
All right.
[SQUEAK]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Officer Murphy?
Turn off the ignition, Mr. Do it!
Out of the car, slowly.
Hey, I thought we discussed this.
You can't scour me without a warrant, or arrest me without--
Spread them.
I can search you if I see a crime happening.
A crime?
What crime?
Is this personal?
Do you-- this is reverse racism.
What are you?
Do not open the trunk.
It looks like, Ruby, Mr. It is Ruby.
You said you never saw her.
Then I saw you taking her down the stairs, Mr.
Listen, you got it all wrong.
I was going to put her in the trunk.
[INAUDIBLE]
Besides, your neighbors ratted you out.
They saw her walking through the front door
earlier this morning.
Relax.
Inside.
I forgot.
I already have a suitcase packed.
Did you take her to the hospital yet?
Richard?
Mrs. Warren, take a seat.
Move.
[GRUNT]
What do you want?
It dawned on me while running her license plate,
why would Ruby risk her own freedom, unless there
was something to risk for?
And then it really, really dawned on me.
You have a multimillion-dollar house.
You own a multimillion-dollar business,
which makes you a multimillion- dollar target.
You thought it was your sexual prowess?
Are you jealous?
[SMACK]
Respect your wife.
This sounds cliche, but I figured
Ruby found out about your safe.
And then you found out about Ruby.
And then she pushed, and then you took care of her.
I never touched her.
She just totally--
[INAUDIBLE] killed herself?
Sounds horrible.
Right, ma'am?
What do you want?
I want what she wanted.
I want what was in that safe.
We know you have one, all three of us.
It's a robbery?
Consider it a withdrawal of one cops, [INAUDIBLE]..
Listen, I don't want to make your roll your donut in prison.
I came for opportunity.
And you take care of me and mine, and now, if you play,
I'll make sure they take you off the noose.
If you refuse, I'll protect and serve your ass, both of you.
Just wait.
I just came home.
I don't have anything to do with this.
Right.
We didn't do anything wrong.
Oh, you didn't do anything wrong.
Hm.
Let me see.
You lied to a police officer, and then
you have a dead felon in the back of the trunk of your car,
and hiding the salami.
Sinner!
Listen to me, you little house-stealing little bitch.
Your balls are my crystal white dice, and I just rolled 9.
So move your ass.
Don't move.
Move it.
Open it.
It's going to take some time.
Hurry up.
Don't fuck with me.
The bank closes at 2:00.
Tell me.
I read that you acquired $10 million worth of property
last year.
Is that correct?
That's correct.
Foreclosed homes in Carson?
Bang on?
Bang on.
Did any of your toxic mortgage victims resemble me?
Look, some of them resembled you.
You know what?
I'm a businessman.
They should have read it before they inscribed ink.
[SMACK]
Shelley Long stopped being a Beverly Hills Girl Scout
master in your bullshit Beverly Hills Girl Scout movie.
[ALARM VIBRATING]
What the fuck is that?
It's my alarm.
It just goes off by itself.
Are you going to kill us?
Not if I [? don't ?] have to.
What the fuck is this?
It's year end.
I deployed the emergency fund.
Been reading the news?
Even movie stars dance to the cage fighter named foreclosure.
I mean, ask Niki Coppola.
That's unfortunate, Dick.
[SLAM]
10-4.
(DISPATCH ON RADIO) 10-4.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you need?
400.
400 what?
$400,000.
$400,000?
That's all?
I got that.
I just don't have it here.
Bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
Just let me go to the bank.
Give me 90 minutes, I've got it for you.
I'd rather call backup.
Backup?
You don't want backup.
You would have come with backup if you wanted backup.
Look, you know you came to get the money,
and we both know that.
So why would you possibly call up your guys?
It's says smaller piece of the pie,
or a chef can't even be in the kitchen.
Listen, just give me 90 minutes.
I'll go to the bank.
I'll come back with a cherry-covered cheesecake pie
worth $400,000.
OK?
Come on.
10-4.
That's a false alarm.
Over.
(DISPATCH ON RADIO) 10-4.
Move.
[GRUNT]
Did you pay him?
I'm fine.
Thanks for asking.
You have 60 minutes.
60 minutes is not enough.
I'll need 90 minutes.
I've got to go fill out forms.
I've got to open the vault. It's just not going to happen.
60 minutes, or I tell them that you're on the run.
Quit looking at her, and go separate mine from yours.
And remember to stash the body.
You're going to kill us?
If he keeps his, I'll keep mine.
Is that Victorian corset comfy?
Of course it is an undergarment.
This is a blouse, and this is a skirt, and professional.
OK.
Don't professionals wear corsets,
I mean, blouses, to the office?
So how do you do it?
Do what?
Remain tranquil in the midst of infidelity?
Why would I tell you that?
Because you're starving for a shoulder to cry on.
Are you hungry?
Does he even care?
I know Carson doesn't care of his, but what about you?
How long has it been Michael Douglas-ing this Glenn Close?
You know, I prefer not to talk.
All right.
Let me show you something.
What are you doing?
Get away from me.
I don't care.
This is why I'm here.
This is why do it, because I'm trying
to protect them, my little girl, my big-head son, and my Harvey
[INAUDIBLE].
Your what?
Harvey Harvey [? Tunes? ?]
What?
Don't look at me like that.
[SIGH] In Carson, we refer to the mentally ill
and handicapped in a particular way.
Herman [? Catnipped, ?] Baby Huey,
and Casper the Friendly Ghost kind of way.
They often act rambunctious, lovable,
but irrationally crazy at times, and very volatile.
And I emphasize pain, because [INAUDIBLE] I'd have smacked me
more than a few times.
Boy, what a left cross.
[LAUGHS]
The $400,000 helps me protect them.
Protect them?
Law enforcement doesn't pay lawyer fees,
nor does it pay for a money-grubbing ex-wife who
keeps begging for alimony, better yet, who
keeps coming after me for alimony
even after she's already moved in with her boss.
She still bugs me for support, and I don't like it.
[SIGH] You know something?
Even after she tried to drown my Harvey son,
and I pressed charges, and a judge
wouldn't even lift a digit.
So I'm doing this to protect them.
[SIGH]
I used to be a teacher.
At 24, I had just earned my masters,
and I thought I could run the world.
I was hired to teach English at El Camino Real High.
And then I married this artist.
And for success, he sacrificed everything,
and it never happened.
And suddenly, my sister died, and my niece Ariel came to us.
And then my husband got lymphoma, and then he died.
But his medical bills lived on, and there wasn't anything
I could do to pay them off.
I faced foreclosure twice.
I couldn't care for my ailing mother.
And fast forward three years, and met this stable real estate
investor.
He knew I was a widow, and that I had a niece.
And it didn't matter.
He took me to Sona on that first date,
and it was very impressive.
Mom was impressed.
She loves his generosity.
It was relieving to have her taken care of.
It was more relieving to have Ariel taken care of.
This was completely unlike my late husband.
So six months later, he asked, and I said yes.
Did I know about Richard?
Yeah, of course, but this isn't his first girlfriend,
and who's going to pay for those medical bills, Ariel's tuition,
and take care of my mom?
I yearn for independence, but independence
takes Benjamin Franklins.
And I'm a laid off teacher.
Hm.
So you upgraded.
Mm-hm.
Do you love him?
Yes I love Richard.
So you married a prince without shiny armor.
Mm.
Oh, my late husband was a king, but a broke King.
Interesting.
I'm sorry.
I probably sound like your ex-wife, or Anna Nicole Smith.
[LAUGHS] Anna Nicole Smith married an 80-year-old man
because she wanted to come up.
I mean, in this economy, who could blame her?
I wish I had big boobs too.
[LAUGHING]
[KISSING]
Stop it.
What?
We both want this.
But I mean, well, if your husband's
slime, what does that make me?
A man who sexually destroyed his wife after nabbing his
[INAUDIBLE].
[MOANING]
Stop it!
What?
[SIGH] I'm the one who's blackmailing
your husband for $400,000.
Remember?
You're stealing $400,000 to protect your family.
That takes grit.
And I like grits.
[KISSING]
You ease up.
You don't like me.
I'm not your ex-husband.
And I don't have your husband's kind of bank.
I'm not your ex-wife, and my first husband died.
I didn't leave him.
So you ease up.
You know what?
You're right.
You're just a rook I'm trying to advance
to a checkmate in this game of revenge fuck.
And you're an extortionist posing as Johnny Law.
We're both just trying to get even.
I'm a guilt-ridden ex police negotiator
who's trying to maintain his semblance of normalcy
and protect his Harvey [INAUDIBLE]..
I misjudged you.
Your judgment was spot on.
Why do you stay with him, continuing
to keep swallowing his semen of indiscretions?
He's my husband.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
You love him.
(PHONE) You have a new text message.
You're early.
[ZIP]
It's all here.
Zip it up.
[ZIP]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
When my mother sought payback for
his philandering disposition.
You came through.
You did yours, I'll do mine.
Because he had so many girlfriends,
he just transformed into quite a fellow.
[SMACK]
[GASP]
Richard!
[SMACK]
[GRUNT]
Richard, stop!
Richard!
[SMACKING]
[GRUNTING]
[CHOKING]
[SMACK]
You jealous shit.
You just ruined us.
[PHONE RINGING]
I have to get this.
That's great, Toby.
He's not going to keep the kids out.
They're innocent.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Can you tell me, he's not Mexican.
He's not Irish.
He's Mexican.
Now I've got to kiss his Mexican ass.
Hey, listen, Toby, this is just wonderful,
but I'm in the middle of a heated disagreement
with my wife right now.
So I've got to go.
Bye.
You're not dragging me to hell.
I had no choice.
I was protecting us.
Do you think the cop's code of silence pertains
to real estate man?
He was going to clean this.
He gave me his word.
When?
When he gave you his cock?
You had to fuck Robocop, didn't you?
What did you do, pull his cock into the side of his leg?
You have no right to judge me.
I was going bonkers, and you had to fuck him, you fucking bitch.
You know what?
Fuck you!
You fucked that bitch.
You caused two deaths.
Fuck you.
OK, OK.
You're upset.
You have a right to be.
Listen, I'm not patronizing you when I say I'm sorry,
but I am sorry.
But I'll utter this.
There's a heap of shit in this house,
and we need to bulldoze it.
You're a fucking asshole.
You murdered a good man!
Good man?
That good man came to rob us.
Listen, just lower the gun.
OK?
You don't want to shoot me.
[CLICK]
OK, maybe you do.
I'm just saying, if you pull that trigger,
there are 3 bodies here, and one of them is a cop.
And your fingerprints are all over that gun.
OK?
Listen, I love you.
Do you hear me?
I love you.
I don't blame you if you leave after I clean this up.
You know I'm going to clean this up, right?
Listen, you know I can clean this up.
This is not a business negotiation.
Everything in our relationship has been business!
OK.
How are you going to clean this?
Put him in the boat, and I'll anchor him in the water.
Dental records?
And a monkey wrench.
What if someone sees us?
And nobody's going to see us.
This plan is solid!
I'm sorry.
OK?
Get the fuck away from me.
OK.
Can I trust you?
Yes.
OK, put the gun in the bag of money, and I'll get the body.
Let's clean the living room.
[SIGH]
[GRUNT]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
I've known for awhile.
Something just seemed off, and I didn't think
you were getting off here.
You know I'm not with you just for your money.
I actually do appreciate you.
Ariel and your mom appreciate me.
I bet she appreciated you.
Did she?
Stop evading, Richard.
Listen, I think maybe we should just clean up.
Richard.
Yeah, she appreciated me.
Listen, we shared common interests, same tastes
in sports, same sense of humor.
There were no asset concerns or income concerns.
Our only concern was having fun.
Just I can't recall the last time
I experienced that with you.
That's shitty.
You wanted to know.
You want to know something?
Ariel and my mom are the only reason
I came back here, because God knows you'll cut them off.
I was going to leave you.
What?
I was going to leave you for her.
Oh.
She didn't have the same problem you do.
I thought you could handle not having children.
I did for two years.
It's not my fault you can't experience motherhood.
You know what?
Go fuck yourself.
What good is having a kingdom if I don't have
any heirs to share it with?
You know, I love Ariel, and I would do anything for her.
She's not my daughter.
I don't have a daughter.
I don't have a son.
Parenthood is more than genetics, Richard.
You know what?
We should never have gotten married,
because I'm not 22, tattooed, Asian,
with bullet-length nipples.
Yeah.
And I'm not bald, 6 foot 3, and built like Ochocinco.
Well, I guess we know each other.
(PHONE) You have a new text message.
Is that his cell?
Yeah.
You took his cell?
Well, I needed to get his keys.
[INAUDIBLE]
It's a text.
It's blocked.
Just a bunch of happy faces.
This truck.
Do you recognize that?
Maybe it's a code or something.
We should change.
[INAUDIBLE]
[WATER RUNNING]
Could you get me the service ladder?
Where is it?
In the walk-in.
Sure.
Thank you, baby.
You're welcome.
[KISS]
What are you doing?
Looking for the garage key.
Don't worry about it.
My mom will get it for you.
[PHONE NOTIFICATION]
Promoters.
Can you hand me that rag?
You don't throw a rag at a woman, jerk.
I'm sorry.
Ugh.
Gees.
Back so soon?
Oh, yeah.
Something came up.
My brother's bachelor party.
Oh, well, sit down.
I'll make you a drink.
Oh, no, no, no.
Not there, honey.
The large bowls go down here.
I thought that they went--
No, no, no.
Here, let me show you.
Oh.
Thank you.
Mm-hm.
Thanks.
Over here.
[SIGH]
[PHONE CLICKING]
Lake closed?
Oh, yeah.
Bachelor party tonight.
Was that your cell phone I heard upstairs?
Yeah.
Just some club promoters.
You work with the mentally impaired.
Excuse me?
Well, you have a pride sticker.
Do you work with special ed kids?
My brother's best friend has an autistic child.
Oh, of course.
Yeah.
[SIGH]
[PHONE CLICKING]
(PHONE) You have a new text message.
Yeah.
Damn promoters again, huh?
Yeah, they're linked.
Hey, Devin, I was thinking, if you keep your number
blocked, Candace won't be able to reach us.
So did you call the phone company yet?
Truck.
It was nice to put a face with the name.
[SIGH] Did Simon tell you about the fugitive?
Mm.
She's not a fugitive.
She's my sister.
You actually thought she wanted you, huh?
Wow.
Don't move!
Now this was supposed to be like a trip
to Chuck-E-Cheese, easy, simple, uncomplicated.
But complications seem to follow $400,000.
I spent weeks with your niece, searching her belongings,
observing her cattiness, seemingly a monumental waste
of time.
Then I discovered something monumental.
She loved to converse, an open book
who briefed me about a book that could change my life.
A very, very expensive book, Mrs. Warren's
literary anthology book.
But my sister tells me it's penniless.
I don't know what you mean.
The $400,000 cashier's check in your wife's anthology.
It isn't here.
Yeah.
I deposited it this week.
So it seems.
And my sister never told me she left.
So I sent our friend, Simon.
Now he never would have killed you.
Maybe it's his Harvey [INAUDIBLE]
or his police guilt. But he is reliable.
So when I stop receiving his texts,
I know it's a cluster fuck.
Now where are they?
[SMACK]
[GASP]
Oh, my god.
Devin, put that gun down!
Why are you still talking?
Such your fucking trap.
Now sit down and shut up!
Amber, Simon, come out.
Amber, Simon.
They left.
Nonsense.
Richard has Simon's cell phone, and Amber's car is outside.
Simon didn't tell you?
You don't want to know.
You know, you remind me of my students.
They always make me repeat myself.
I hate to repeat myself.
Where are they?
They're dead.
You killed them?
No, no, no.
I didn't kill anybody.
Ruby fell.
[SMACK]
(SCREAMING) Stop!
Take it easy.
OK?
Shut up!
[SCREAM]
Where are they?
[GRUNT]
They're in the trunk.
Do you have the keys to the garage?
Richard.
You open it.
Get up.
Move.
Move!
Uh-huh.
Your door stopper.
Listen, I'm sorry there's nothing I could do.
Son of a bitch!
[SMACK]
Oh, god!
How could you?
She was 25!
There was nothing I could do.
She just fell.
And I'm supposed to believe you?
Hm?
It's not my fault. I didn't touch her.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
You're used to getting what you want.
Right?
How you want it, when you want it.
Well, not today, motherfucker.
There are consequences for our actions.
Those are not my fucking actions, asshole.
She fell.
I had nothing to do with that.
Now, the other one, I admit, I'm my father's son.
He's fucked my wife, so I did that one.
[SIGH] Well, I guess today's going
to be a good day and a bad day for her.
Right?
[YELLING]
[CLICK]
Stop.
Listen to me.
She's the only one who knows where the money is.
I have no idea.
If you shoot her, your stash is gone.
Cops are going to come for you, just like they did.
They hunted down Bin Laden, and he was a billionaire.
If you're a trillionaire, great.
We can both come out winners.
Come on, man.
Christ, I'm begging you.
What am I supposed to do?
Just go ahead and sell out my friends
like I'm some weasel like you?
Huh?
Yeah.
They're dead.
OK?
Come on.
[INAUDIBLE]
I'll get your back.
I'll totally get your back.
That's not a problem.
How do I know that motor tongue here won't start her engine?
Yeah.
But she knows if she does, her aunt is gone.
We have as much to lose as you do.
OK.
You know where it is?
It's in the kitchen.
Awesome.
I love sandwiches.
Let's move!
[GROWL]
[INAUDIBLE],, I will end your niece
if you attempt any heroics.
Go.
What's this about?
Why me?
Three years ago this parasitic [INAUDIBLE] company, the Warren
Investment Group, who purchased my mother's
[INAUDIBLE] home, a home given to me, Trucker Miller my sister
Amber Miller.
And after settling failed loan modifications
and unsuccessful class action lawsuits,
my sister asked us day and night for someone
to help us secure our home.
And for safety, we kept our brother Dennis behind,
because the new owner didn't want any vagrants
on the property.
Dennis never made it off the property.
And after that, the Warren Group rejected our loan.
So we went off, and then we shacked up
with his friend, Simon.
I guess being the negotiator that
couldn't prevent his best friend's death
kind of got to him.
So he just let us stay with him in spite of that.
In spite of all of that, no teacher, firemen,
or even a donut-shitting cop like Simon
is immune from this recession.
Did you know his home forecloses on Monday?
Hm?
After evaluating our options, we found answers to our prayers.
You, Richard Warren.
See, we know your history with ladies,
and you had never seen our faces.
So it was easy for Amber to con you.
And the whole thing disturbs me.
It sickens me, the idea of your penis
swimming around in my sister.
But you know what sickens me even more?
My brother died over a house.
A fucking house you refused to give back
to us even after we paid you.
This is a post-modern society, Richard,
and God favors the ruthless.
And you know this better than anybody else.
So I'd rather March with Attila the Hun than
MLK if he pays my rent.
Oh, you look at me.
What's the hold up, Aunt Hedda?
Get my fucking money!
Open it.
[ZIP]
Bring it.
What are you doing?
[GRUNT]
[GUNSHOT]
[SCREAM]
[CRYING]
Richard, are you OK?
Ariel, go upstairs right now and get my medical kit.
[GROANING]
It's better me than you and my daughter.
[GUNSHOTS]
What the fuck was that?
Remember you said that I could leave when this is over?
Well, it's over.
Put down the gun.
I'm through swallowing your semen of indiscretions.
Don't do this.
I have $400,000, and I don't need you anymore.
And I don't love you.
Hedda.
And I don't think I ever did.
And I'm not afraid to admit that.
Put down the gun.
This is for Simon.
Aunt Hedda, is everything OK?
What are you doing?
Ariel, he killed those two people in that trunk.
That's not true.
If I don't do this, he'll kill us.
So you're going to kill him?
He's a monster and can not be trusted.
Put down the gun.
Get out of the way.
He's not even your real uncle.
Well, he treats me like he's my uncle.
Why?
Because he bought you a fucking BMW?
Get the fuck out of the way!
[SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[COUGHING]
[GASP]
[GRUNT]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[PHONE RINGING]
So what do you think of the baby?
Oh, he's pretty cute.
Cute, right?
Yeah.
He's a little hairy.
He reminds me of Chewbacca.
[LAUGHS] Oh.
I always wondered why babies are so hairy.
Mr. Warren, Mrs. Warren, it's me, Jahira.
Fernando forgot his watch.
[SCREAMING]
No, no, no, no.
Don't look.
Don't.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, go call the cops.
OK?
Go call the cops.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Fuck.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
Warren residence.
No, no, no, no.
This is his housekeeper.
Yeah, well, there's a pretty good reason
why he hasn't been answering his calls.
Yeah.
He told the news.
He sent the Sheriff's packing, because the people
wouldn't leave the house.
Good thinking.
People who can't pay their house loan shouldn't be kicked out.
No way.
No.
We were here earlier.
We just came back for my watch.
Toby, everybody's dead here.
I swear!
Yeah.
OK.
Yeah, take care.
[ZIP]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Richard!
Richard, it's Toby!
I've been calling you all day.
House wouldn't back me up.
Oh, my goodness.
What the-- oh, my goodness.
Well, I guess you screwed with the wrong guy this time,
asshole.
[SIGH]